dripbook.com 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy | Dripbook

Dripbook.com recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use Dripbook.com or other web sites owned or operated by Dadaphile, Inc. (the “Dripbook Websites”) (collectively or individually “Users”) value their privacy. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Dripbook Websites. Dripbook.com provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Dripbook Websites. 

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Dripbook.com Terms of Use. Your use of the Dripbook Websites and any personal information you provide on the Dripbook Websites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use. 

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the Dripbook Websites becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice. 

##  The Information Dripbook.com Collects 

  * We collect and process all your personal data in accordance with the relevant data protection regulations, in particular the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) and the German Telemedia Act (TMG). This means that we may process your personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy with your consent. We may use the information we collect from you when you register, use its services, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features for various purposes. 
  * User Provided Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and e-mail address) to Dripbook.com when choosing to participate in various activities on the Dripbook Websites such as uploading images, videos, posting messages in our forums, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. Dripbook.com will not distribute or publish your e-mail address to any third party for any reason without your prior written consent. 
  * Cookies Information: When you visit the Dripbook Websites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Dripbook.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Dripbook Websites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. The Dripbook Websites may also use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve relevant ads targeting the Dripbook Websites to those who have visited the Dripbook Websites. If you wish to control whether and how the Dripbook Websites use cookies to serve relevant ads to you, please visit Google's [ Ads Preferences Manager ](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) and also refer to the [ Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. ](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) You may also explore your browser's [ "Do Not Track" ](http://donottrack.us/) settings for cookies. 
  * Log File Information: When you use the Dripbook Websites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 
  * Sensitive Information: We do not collect sensitive information, such as race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union memberships, genetic or biometric data, health or mortality, sex life or sexual orientation. 

##  The Way Dripbook.com Uses Information 

  * If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Dripbook Websites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Dripbook Websites. 
  * Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload content or send messages through the Dripbook Websites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any content that you submit to the Dripbook Websites (other than your e-mail address and payment information) may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major changes to the Dripbook Websites or for customer service purposes). 
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Dripbook Websites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 
  * We use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Dripbook Websites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

##  When Dripbook Discloses Information 

  * We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 
  * We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Dripbook Websites. 
  * We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 
  * Dripbook.com also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that Dripbook.com believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Dripbook.com, our Users or others. 

##  Your Choices 

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Dripbook Websites, in which case Dripbook.com may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and e-mail preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

Please contact Dripbook.com with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices using this contact form. 

##  Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites 

Ads appearing on the Dripbook Websites may be delivered to users by Dripbook.com or one of our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Dripbook.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Dripbook.com does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Dripbook Websites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. Dripbook's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

##  Our Commitment To Data Security 

Dripbook.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Dripbook.com and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Dripbook.com makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If Dripbook.com learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Dripbook.com may post a notice on the Dripbook Websites if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us. 

##  Our Commitment To Childrens' Privacy 

In order to register for an account on the Dripbook Websites, a user must be over the 18 years of age and agree to abide by and be bound by our Terms of Use. Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Dripbook.com does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Dripbook Websites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Dripbook Websites at any time or in any manner. If Dripbook.com learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Dripbook Websites without verified parental consent, then Dripbook.com will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

##  In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy 

In the event that Dripbook.com is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

##  Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice 

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Dripbook Websites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions. 

##  Contacting us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: 

Dripbook   

##  Date Last Modified 

This Privacy Notice was last modified May 29, 2018.
